[
    {
        "number": 1,
        "question": "What is the outcome of this code?",
        "code": "",
        "answers": [ 
            "Both loops print concurrently", 
            "5 diamonds are printed, followed by 5 hearts",
            "Does not compile",
            "Causes race condition",
            "Crahes because of deadlock", 
            "Causes priority inversion"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 1
    }, 
    {
        "number": 2,
        "question": "What is the outcome of this code?",
        "code": "",
        "answers": [ 
            "Loop A always finishes first", 
            "Loop B always finishes first",
            "Order is not guaranteed", 
            "Does not compile",
            "Causes race condition"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 2
    }, 
    {
        "number": 3,
        "question": "What is the outcome of this code?",
        "code": "",
        "answers": [ 
            "All loops print concurrently", 
            "It prints numbers 1 through 5, followed by 5 diamonds, followed by 5 hearts",
            "Does not compile",
            "Causes race condition",
            "Crahes because of deadlock", 
            "Causes priority inversion"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 1
    }, 
    {
        "number": 4,
        "question": "What is the outcome of this code?",
        "code": "",
        "answers": [  
            "It runs without issues", 
            "It runs UI code on background thread",
            "Does not compile",
            "Causes race condition",
            "Crahes because of deadlock", 
            "Causes priority inversion"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 4
    }, 
    {
        "number": 5,
        "question": "What is the outcome of this code?",
        "code": "",
        "answers": [ 
            "It will always print four moons before four suns", 
            "It will always print four suns before four moons",
            "The order is not guaranteed",
            "Does not compile",
            "Causes race condition",
            "Crahes because of deadlock", 
            "Causes priority inversion"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 2
    }, 
    {
        "number": 6,
        "question": "What is the outcome of this code?",
        "code": "",
        "answers": [ 
            "processImage(data:) will always return nil", 
            "Does not compile: cannot convert DispatchQueue to UIImage?",
            "processImage(data:) returns the tinted image as intended",
            "Causes race condition",
            "Crahes because of deadlock", 
            "Causes priority inversion"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 2
    }, 
    {
        "number": 7,
        "question": "What is the outcome of this code?",
        "code": "",
        "answers": [ 
            "Five cows are printed, followed by five dogs", 
            "Both loops will run concurrently, order not guaranteed",
            "Causes race condition",
            "Crahes because of deadlock", 
            "Causes priority inversion"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 1
    }, 
    {
        "number": 8,
        "question": "What is the outcome of this code?",
        "code": "",
        "answers": [ 
            "Prints 1 through 5, then 0 through 9", 
            "Prints 0 through 9",
            "Order of printed digits is not guaranteed",
            "Causes race condition",
            "Crahes because of deadlock", 
            "Causes priority inversion"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 3
    }, 
    {
        "number": 9,
        "question": "What is the outcome of this code?",
        "code": "",
        "answers": [ 
            "Results are always printed in the same order"
            "Order of printed results is not guaranteed",
            "Causes race condition",
            "Crahes because of deadlock", 
            "Causes priority inversion"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 0
    }, 
    {
        "number": 10,
        "question": "What is the outcome of this code?",
        "code": "",
        "answers": [ 
            "Prints 1 through 30 in order",
            "Prints 11 through 20, then 1 through 10, then 21 through 30",
            "Order of printed digits is not guaranteed",
            "Causes race condition",
            "Crahes because of deadlock", 
            "Causes priority inversion"
        ],
        "correct_answer": 0
    }
]
